

# CONTACT

+380(93)6639196

kondratenko666olga@gmail.com

<u>Linkedin</u>

Github

Kyiv, Ukraine

## **TECH SKILLS**

- HTML5/CSS3
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- Parcel
- Node.js

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Attention to detail
- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Good communication

# **LANGUAGES**

English - Upper-Intermediate
Ukrainian - Native
Russian - Native

# **OLHA KONDRATENKO**

# Junior Fullstack developer

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a Junior Fullstack Developer with a real passion for web development. My knowledge includes HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, as well as the first steps in React. I study modern technologies and practice them.

My strong point is analytical thinking. I am able to analyze problems and look for solutions to accurately solve technical problems. I am always open to learning and ready to improve my skills.

I have my first practical experience working on web projects and I feel comfortable in teamwork. My goal is to create useful and efficient web applications that make users' daily lives easier.

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

# <u>Developer portfolio</u> | <u>Link</u> (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

A website of developer where represents the completed progects and all needed information and most popular questions. Responsive design, transform effects, modal windows and a fidbeack form.

Role: Developer.

# Photograph portfolio | Link (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

A website of professional photographer. Responsive design, transform effects, modal windows and a fidbeack form.

Role: Developer.

# <u>Web site for social organisation</u> | <u>Link</u> (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

A website of social organisation to represent the activietis of the organisation all actual progects and events. Responsive design.

Role: Design creetor, Developer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Web developer

SELECT LOGISTICS INC | June 2024 - present

- Bug fixing
- Website mantaining
- Writing scripts for automatisation of work processes

# Accountant of the international department

SELECT LOGISTICS INC | Feb 2023 - present

- Communication with contractors;
- Control over payments;
- Maintaining planned and actual budgets;

#### **EDUCATION**

### IT School GoIT

Fullstack Developer | 2023 - 2024

### Perspective - XXI century

web design and website layout | 2016

#### Academy of Municipal Administration

Documentation and information activities | 2014 - 2016